Guide to the River Oaks Rose Club Records
University of Houston Libraries
River Oaks Rose Club records
1974-2014
02/2015-003
River Oaks Rose Club
5.00 linear feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
This collection includes photos of Rose Club events, yearbooks that catalog membership, secretarial records and correspondence, and several scrapbooks. The majority of the materials are arranged chronologically and in the order they were received from donors.
Historical Note:
The River Oaks Rose Club was established as an organization for rose lovers and gardeners to share advice, maintain their gardens, and create community. The club held monthly meetings and exhibited an annual Rose Show to showcase members’ hard work.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
River Oaks Rose Club
Genre/Form of Material:
Administrative records; Photograph Albums; Photographs; Scrapbooks; Yearbooks
Geographic Name:
River Oaks (Tex.)
Topical Term:
Gardening; Women -- Societies and clubs -- Texas -- Houston
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research
Related Materials:
River Oaks Blossom Club
Information about related materials is available at http://archon.lib.uh.edu/index.php?p=collections/controlcard&id=21&q=blossom
Physical Characteristics or Technical Requirements:
Digital archival materials can be accessed in the Special Collections Reading Room by advance request. These materials may require up to one week to access. Contact curator Vince Lee at velee@uh.edu for more information.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes photos of Rose Club events, yearbooks that catalog membership, secretarial records and correspondence, and several scrapbooks. The majority of the materials are arranged chronologically and in the order they were received from donors.
Detailed List of Contents
- Rose Club Yearbooks/Guest Lists, id165141
  - Yearbooks 73-85, 1973-1985; id165147 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Yearbooks 85-94, 1985-1994; id165148 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Yearbooks 94-02, 1994-2002; id165149 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Yearbooks 02-06, 2002-2006; id165150 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Yearbooks 06-11, 2006-2011; id165151 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Yearbooks 11-14, 2011-2014; id165152 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Guest Book, 1991; id165153 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - Guest Book, 2004; id165154 (Box 2, Item 2)
- Photographs and Scrapbooks, id165142
  - Photographs and Photograph Albums, id165155
    - Miscellaneous Photos, undated; id165166 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Photo Album, 1979; id165159 (Box 2, Item 3)
    - Black and White Photo Album, undated; id165160 (Box 2, Item 4)
    - Pastel Floral Album, undated; id165161 (Box 2, Item 5)
    - Photo Album, 2005; id165162 (Box 2, Item 6)
    - Green and White Floral Album, undated; id165163 (Box 2, Item 7)
    - Photo Album, 2004; id165164 (Box 2, Item 8)
  - Scrapbooks, id165157
    - River Oaks Rose Club 97-98, 1997-1998; id165170 (Ovsbox 3, Item 1)
    - River Oaks Rose Club 00-01, 2000-2001; id165171 (Ovsbox 3, Item 2)
    - River Oaks Rose Club 05-06, 2005-2006; id165172 (Ovsbox 3, Item 3)
    - River Oaks Rose Club 02-03, 2002-2003; id165173 (Ovsbox 3, Item 4)
    - River Oaks Rose Club 04-05, 2004-2005; id165174 (Ovsbox 4, Item 1)
    - River Oaks Rose Club 01-02, 2001-2002; id165175 (Ovsbox 4, Item 2)
    - River Oaks Rose Club 03-04, 2003-2004; id165176 (Ovsbox 5, Item 1)
- Secretary's Records, id165143
  - Secretarial Records 75-77, 1975-1977; id165179 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Secretarial Records 70-79, 1970-1979; id165180 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Secretarial Records 81-90, 1981-1990; id165181 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Secretarial Records 90-95, 1990-1995; id165182 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Secretarial Records 95-00, 1995-2000; id165183 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Secretarial Records 00-10, Part One, 2000-2010; id165184 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Secretarial Records 00-10, Part Two, 2000-2010; id165185 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Secretarial Records 00-10, Part Three, 2000-2010; id165186 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Secretarial Records 09-10, 2009-2010; id165187 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Secretarial Records 11-20, 2011-2020; id165188 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Secretarial Records 12-13, Part One, 2012-2013; id165189 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Secretarial Records 12-13, Part Two, 2012-2013; id165190 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Records, id165144
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes digital archival materials, which are indicated by the term [digital]. A digital copy of the CD can be accessed in the Special Collections Reading Room by advance request. These materials may require up to one week to access. Contact curator Vince Lee (velee@uh.edu) for more information.
  - Correspondence, 2013; id165192 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Invitations, 2006-2014; id165193 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Brochures and Invoices, 2003-2013; id165194 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - River Oaks Rose Club Flower Show, 1984-1985; id165195 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - RORGC 2006 CD [digital], id165196 (Box 6, Item 1)